Guide to the Yale Repertory Theatre Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the Yale Repertory Theatre, circa 1941-2001; Accession 2003-A-022
  - Yale Rep Sessions# 3 (Box 16)
  - August Wilson's Sacred Book, MPR, 1988 (Box 16)
  - Rep # Radio Ad -Proposes (Box 16)
  - Way of the World Raw Audio (Box 16)
  - Troiilus and Cressida, P.Joffee (Box 16)
  - Radio Spots-Library (Box 16)
  - Venus ATC, 1996 (Box 16)
  - Venus ATC, NPR, 1996 (Box 16)
  - Night Mama (Box 16)
  - Yale Rep-Solid Gold Cadillac-WLIS (Box 16)
  - Henry Winkler Yale Rep Promo (Box 16)
  - The Stephen Holt Show Onstage America, 1989 (Box 16)
  - CTV 175 (Box 16)
  - Heaven WTNH, 2000 (Box 16)
  - Victoria Nocan WTNH_TV, 2001 (Box 16)
  - The Birds (Box 16)
  - (Blank) (Box 16)
  - Yale Rep. The Imaginary Invalid, 1999 (Box 16)
  - CTV Today, 1999 (Box 16)
  - The Spirit of New Haven Symphony Orchestra, 1999 (Box 16)
  - Yale Rep Presents:Betrayal, 1999 (Box 16)
  - Big Night, 2001 (Box 16)
  - Yale Rep: A Cup of Coffee, 2001 (Box 16)
  - Yale Rep: Betrayal, 1999 (Box 16)
  - Yale Rep: The Imaginary Invalid, 1999 (Box 16)
  - Yale Rep: Curse of the Starving Class, 1999 (Box 16)
  - Yale Rep: Rice Boy, 2000 (Box 16)
  - Season Photos (Box 16)
  - Oleanna Footage, 1993-1994 (Box 16)
  - (Blank) (Box 16)
  - The Joseph M. McDade Center for literary and Performing Arts, 1993 (Box 16)
  - 58 Second PSA (Box 16)
  - AWGN_TV Original Production :A Stage of Our Own (Box 16)
  - Yale Rep:Rice Boy (Box 16)
  - (Blank)/ (Box 16)
  - For Joe Griffasi (Box 16)
  - Yale Rep: A Cup of Coffee (Box 16)
  - Yale Rep: The Curse of the Starving Class (Box 16)
  - Tree (Box 16)
  - Yale Rep: Richard III, 2000 (Box 16)
  - Yale Rep: Heaven, 2000 (Box 16)
  - Yale Rep: The Way of the World, 2001 (Box 16)
  - Yale Rep: Heaven, 2000 (Box 16)
  - The Birds (Box 16)
  - Misc (Box 17)
  - Ma Rainey's Black Bottom (Box 17)
  - 97 QWK Season DSA dub (Box 17)
  - 02439 -All the Bells,02440 Turntable-Season DSA dub (Box 17)
  - Yale Rep_Iphigeneia at Aulis-5 Broadcast clips (Box 17)
  - YSD at Yale Rep-You Can Never Tell, 2001 (Box 17)
  - YSD at Yale Rep-Betty's Summer Vacation, 2002 (Box 17)
  - YSD at Yale Rep-Kingdom of Earth, 2001 (Box 17)
  - Yale Rep presents Big Night (Box 17)
  - Iphigenia at Aulis TV cuts, 2002 (Box 17)
  - Yale Rep presents -Big Night (Box 17)
  - YSD at Yale Rep-Kingdom of Earth, 2001 (Box 17)
  - YSD aT Yale Rep-You can Never Tell, 2001 (Box 17)
  - YSD at Yale Rep-Betty's Summer Vacation, 2001 (Box 17)
  - Serious Money, 2002 (Box 17)
  - School Shows (Box 18)
  - Three Sisters, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Titus, 1988 (Box 18)
  - The Tempest, 1988 (Box 18)
  - Three Sisters, 2001 (Box 18)
  - Tragedy of Hamlet, 1990 (Box 18)
  - The Trial, 2002 (Box 18)
  - True Blue and Trembling, 1986-1987 (Box 18)
  - Troy Women, 1997 (Box 18)
  - Twelth Night, 1990 (Box 18)
  - The Vultures, 1983-1984 (Box 18)
  - Waiting for Godot, 1995 (Box 18)
  - Watertown Primary, 1985-1986 (Box 18)
  - Wild Honey, 1995 (Box 18)
  - The Winter's Tale, 1977-1978 (Box 18)
  - Winter's Tale, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Winter's Tale, 1931 (Box 18)
  - Women Beware Women, 1972-1973 (Box 18)
  - Women Beware Women, 1979-1980 (Box 18)
  - Yegor Bolychor ant the Others, 1978-1979 (Box 18)
  - Misc (Box 19)
  - Galileo, 1991 (Box 19)
  - Crumbs for the Table of Joy, 1997-1998 (Box 19)
  - Measure for Measure, 1997-1998 (Box 19)
  - Great Men of Science, 1998 (Box 19)
  - Advertising New Season, 1998-1999 (Box 19)
  - Renewal Campaign Letter, 1998-1999 (Box 19)
  - Direct mail Campaign Request bid, 1998-1999 (Box 19)
  - The Glass Menagerie, 1994 (Box 19)
  - Hay Fever, 1996 (Box 19)
  - Advertising, 1997-1998 (Box 19)
  - Advertising New Journal, 1997-1998 (Box 19)
  - Advertising Yale Herald, 1997-1998 (Box 19)
  - Advertising WNHC, 1997-1998 (Box 19)
  - Candida, 1997-1998 (Box 19)
  - Splash Hatch on the E Going Down, 1997-1998 (Box 19)
  - Metro Line, 1998 (Box 19)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1997-1998 (Box 19)
  - The Yale Herald News, 1998 (Box 19)
  - The Cure of Troy, 1997-1998 (Box 19)
  - Metro Line, 1998 (Box 19)
  - Petersburg, 1997-1998 (Box 19)
  - Seasonal, 1997-1998 (Box 19)
  - Numbers (Box 19)
  - Pilgrims of the Night, 1995-1996 (Box 19)
  - School Show Binders (Box 20)
  - People Vs. God of Vengeance, 2000 (Box 20)
  - The Misanthrope, 2000 (Box 20)
  - The Way of the World Maheting, 2001 (Box 20)
  - The Golem, 1999 (Box 21)
  - Life is a Dream, 1999 (Box 21)
  - The Seagull, 1997 (Box 21)
  - Fatty Arbuckle Spook House Revue, 1998 (Box 21)
  - The Road, 1998 (Box 22)
  - Twelfth Night, 1998 (Box 22)
  - Prince of Homburg, 1999 (Box 22)
  - Crazy Locomotive, 1999 (Box 22)
- Slides of theatrical performances, 1975-1998; Accession 2003-A-157
  The materials are open for research.
  - About Face; W. B. Carter, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ah, Wilderness; Gerry Goldstein, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Alchemist; Gerry Goldstein, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The American Play; T. Charles Erickson, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Amnestia, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Amy Bock; T. Charles Erickson, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Antigone in New York; T. Charles Erickson, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Apochalyptic Butterflies; W. B. Carter, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Art of Success; T. Charles Erickson, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - As I Lay Dying; Gerry Goldstein, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Astapovo; W. B. Carter (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - As You Like It (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - As You Like It, 1978-79 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - As You Like It; T. Charles Erickson, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - An Attempt at Flying; Gerry Goldstein, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Baal, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - The Bakkai; Steve Wolf, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Baltamore Waltz; T. Charles Erickson (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - The Bath House; Paul J. Penders, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - The Beach; Gerry Goldstein, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Beauty Part, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The Beaux Stratogen; T. Charles Erickson, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Benten Kozo, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Between East and West (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - The Bewitched, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Big Divinity, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Bingo (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - The Birthday Party; George G. Slade, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - The Blind; T. Charles Erickson, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Blood Knot; W. B. Carter, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Blood Wedding; Ian Straker, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Boesman and Lena; Gerry Goldstein, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Bosoms; Gerry Goldstein, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Bricklayers; Gerry Goldstein, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Candida, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 34a)
  - Cemetery Club; W. B. Carter, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Cherry Orchard; T. Charles Erickson, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Children of Paradise (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Child's Play; W. B. Carter, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Chopin; W. B. Carter, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Chute Roosters; Gerry Goldstein, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Cobb, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - The Colored Museum; T. Charles Erickson (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Crazy Love; W. B. Carter, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - The Cryptogram; T. Charles Erickson, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - The Cure at Troy, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 44a)
  - Curse of the Starving Class; Gerry Goldstein, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Da of the Picnic; W.B. Carter, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Daylight in Exile; Gerry Goldstein, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - The Death of the Last Black Man, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Democracy in America, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Dinosaurs; Gerry Goldstein, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Diva Studies; T. Charles Erickson, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Doctor Faustus Lights The; Paul J. Penders, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Don Juan; T. Charles Erickson (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Doll's House; W.B. Carter, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - The Dragon; Paul J. Penders, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Drums in the Night, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Duchess of Malfi, 1975-76 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Duchess of Malfi; T. Charles Erickson, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - The Dutchman (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Edward the Second; T. Charles Erickson, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Electra; Paul J. Penders, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Elizabeth; W.B. Carter, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Escape from Happiness, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Exact Change; W.B. Carter, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Family Rites, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Fanshen; George G. Slade, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - The Fatty Arbuckle Spook House Revue; T. Charles Erickson, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Faulkner's Bicycle, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Fefu and Her Friends, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Fences; W.B. Carter, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Figaro Figaro; T. Charles Erickson, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - First Lady; T. Charles Erickson, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Frogs, 1973-74 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Fuente Ovejuna; T. Charles Erickson (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - General Gorgeous (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Geography, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 75a)
  - The Green Bird, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Hamlet; T. Charles Erickson (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Heartbreak House; W.B. Carter, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Hedda Gabler; Gerry Goldstein, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Hello Goodbye; W.B. Carter, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Henry IV, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Importance of Being Earnest; W.B. Carter, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Intermezzo; Gerry Goldstein, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Interrogating the Nude; Gerry Goldstein, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Ivanov; Gerry Goldstein, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Johnny Bull; Gerry Goldstein, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Kiss of the Spider Woman; Gerry Goldstein, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Landscape of the Body; T. Charles Erickson, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Largo Desolation; Gerry Goldstein, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Le Bourgeois Avant-Garde; T. Charles Erickson, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Le Cirque Invisible, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - A Lesson from Aloes; Gerry Goldstein, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Little Eyole; Paul J. Penders, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Long Day's Journey into Night; Gerry Goldstein, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Love Labor's Lost; Gerry Goldstein, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Magnificent Cuckold; Gerry Goldstein, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Mahagony, 1978-79 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Man is Man (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Marrige; 2 W. B. Carter- Paul Penders, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Master Harold and the Boys; Gerry Goldstein, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Measure for Measure; Gerry Goldstein, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Medea; Paul J. Penders, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Melons; Gerry Goldstein, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 103a)
  - The Miser; Gerry Goldstein, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Miss Julie; Gerry Goldstein, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Mistaken Identities, 1978-79 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - A Moon for the Misbegotten; Gerry Goldstein, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Moon over Miami; Gerry Goldstein, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Mrs. Warren's Profession; T. Charles Erickson, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Mrs. Warren's Profession; Gerry Goldstein, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - My Children My Africa, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - The My House Party; Gerry Goldstein, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Neddy; Gerry Goldstein, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Ohio State Murders; Gerry Goldstein, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Oleanna; T. Charles Erickson (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - On The Verge, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Othello; Paul J. Penders, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Pentecost; T. Charles Erickson, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Petersburg, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 118a)
  - Phaedra and Hippolytus; Gerry Goldstein, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - The Piano Lesson; Gerry Goldstein, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Pill Hill; Gerry Goldstein, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - A Place with the Pigs; Gerry Goldstein, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Playboy of the West Indies, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Pygmalion, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Rip Van Winkle; Gerry Goldstein, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Rum and Cake; W. F. V, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Rust and Rain; Gerry Goldstein, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Saint Joan of the Stockyards; T. Charles Erickson, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Sarcophagus; Gerry Goldstein (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Scapin; Gerry Goldstein, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - School for Wives; T. Charles Erickson, 191993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Search and Destroy, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Sganerelle (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - The Size of the World; Gerry Goldstein, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - The Skin of Our Teeth; T. Charles Erickson, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Slavs!; Richard Anderson, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Splash Hatch on the E Going Down, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 136a)
  - Solid Gold Cadillac; Gerry Goldstein, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - Starting Monday; Gerry Goldstein, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Stitchers; W. B. Carter, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Suicide; Gerry Goldstein, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Summer and Smoke; Gerry Goldstein, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - Sweet Life; W. B. Carter, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Talley's Folly; W. B. Carter, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Tartuffe; W. B. Carter, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - They Are Dying Out; Gerry Goldstein, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Thunder Knocking at the Door; T. Charles Erickson, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Ties That Bind (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Timon of Athens; Gerry Goldstein, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Titus, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Touch of the Poet; W. B. Carter, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - Triumph of Love; Richard Anderson, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - Troilus and Cressida, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 152)
  - Troilus and Cressida, 1975-76 (Box 6, Folder 153)
  - Twelfth Night; T. Charles Erickson, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Two Trains Running; Gerry Goldstein, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - Ubu Rex; Gerry Goldstein, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - Uncle Vanya; T. Charles Erickson, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - Underground, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 158)
  - Venus; T. Charles Erickson, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 159)
  - The Wall of Water; Gerry Goldstein, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 161)
  - Watergate Follies, 1973-74 (Box 6, Folder 162)
  - Wild Duck, 1977-78 (Box 6, Folder 163)
  - Wings; Eugene Cook, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 164)
  - Winter's Tale; W. B. Carter, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 165)
- 2002-2003 season scripts, Accession 2004-A-011
  - Scripts (Box 1)
  - Medea (Box 1)
  - Macbeth (Box 1)
  - Cinderella (Box 1)
  - Breath, Boom (Box 1)
  - Fighting Words (Box 1)
  - Psychic Life of Savages (Box 1)
  - Taming of the Shrew (Box 1)
  - The Black Monk (Box 1)
  - B Roll tape (Box 1)
  - Fighting Words B Roll Tape (Box 1)
  - Psychic Life of Savages B Roll Tape (Box 1)
  - Taming of the Shrew B Roll Tape (Box 1)
  - The Black Monk B Roll Tape (Box 1)
- Records of the managing director and associate managing director, 1982-2003; Accession 2007-A-098
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2038
  - Local Auditions, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
  - YOU NEVER CAN TELL REP 1
    - Dialect Coach, Catherine Fitzmaurice, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Stage Manager, Karen Quisenberry, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
  - KINGDOM OF EARTH REP 2
    - Stage Manager, Courtney Todd, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Dialect Coach, Beth Maguire, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Sound Designer, Fitz Patton, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Financials, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Script, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Casting, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Licensing Agreement, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Director, Mark Rucker, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Rehearsal/Performance Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Rehearsal Schedules/Contact Sheets, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Production Notes, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
  - IT PAYS TO ADVERTISE REP 3
    - Stage Manager, Cynthia Kocher, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
  - BETTY'S SUMMER VACATION REP 4
    - Director, Doug Hughes, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Stage Manager, Lisa Porter, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Sound Designer, David Van Tieghem, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Pension and Health Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Rehearsal/Performance Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Casting, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Rehearsal/Performance Schedules, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - House Management Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
  - SERIOUS MONEY REP 5
    - Director, Jean Randich, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Composer/ Designer, Shane Rettig, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Licensing Agreement, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
  - GEOGRAPHY REP 1
    - Health Info, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Collaborator Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Calendars and schedules, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Injury and health, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Licensing Agreement, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Notes and Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Guest Artist Info, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Rehearsal Notes, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Performance Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Agreement, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Program, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Artist Contracts, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - CANDIDA REP 2
    - Performance Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Program, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Guest Artists (actors), 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Contact sheet, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Performance Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Rehearsal Notes, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - SPLASH HATCH REP 3
    - Rehearsal Notes, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Co-Production Budget, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Notes and Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Contact Sheet, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Sound Designer, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Costume Designer, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Co-Production Agreement, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Guest Artist (actor), 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Program, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - MIDSUMMER REP 4
    - Musicians, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Rehearsal notes, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Director, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Notes and Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Composer, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Guest Artist (actor), 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Press Release, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - CURE AT TROY REP 5
    - Symposium, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Composer, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Performance Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Rehearsal Notes, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Notes and correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Press release, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Contact Sheet, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Guest Artists (actors), 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - SCHOOL SHOWS, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - PETERSBURG, 1997-1998
    - Performance Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Rehearsal Notes, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Contact Sheets, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Guest Artist (actor), 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - THE SEAGULL, 1997-1998
    - Licensing agreement, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - The Blind Mice, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - The Blind, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - The Road, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - The Road Misc., 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - Fatty Arbuckle Licensing Agreement, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - Fatty Arbuckle Chris Jeffries contract, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - THE GREAT MAGICIAN, 2002-2003
    - Recording Rider, 2002-2003 (Box 3)
    - Magician Contracts, 2002-2003 (Box 3)
  - THE BOOK OF TWO recording rider, 2002-2003 (Box 3)
  - The Winter's Tale Gabe Mahler (actor), 2002-2003 (Box 3)
  - Housing 2002-2003 Season (Box 3)
  - El Dorado Cable Bills FY 03, 2002-2003 (Box 3)
  - Long Wharf Apt. Rentals, 2002-2003 (Box 3)
  - University Properties Schiavone Corr., 2002-2003 (Box 3)
  - MEDEA/MCBETH/CINDERELLA, 2002-2003
    - Rehearsal accompanist, 2002-2003 (Box 3)
    - Rogers and Hammerstein, 2002-2003 (Box 3)
    - Auditions Kids New Haven, 2002-2003 (Box 3)
    - Press and Marketing memos, 2002-2003 (Box 3)
    - Payroll, 2002-2003 (Box 3)
    - Correspondence and notes, 2002-2003 (Box 3)
    - Musician Search, 2002-2003 (Box 3)
  - THE TRIAL YSD 3 licensing agreement, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - A STREETCAR NAMED DESIRE YSD 2 licensing agreement, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - THREE SISTERS YSD1 licensing agreement, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - THREE SISTERS prod. notes, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - 1st year Acting Project, Elinor Holdgridge, Director, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - Bundy Launch, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - Purification of the Heart/PT3 T. Harris, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - YSD Miscellaneous contracts, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - Garrison Keillor/LIFE OF COMEDY, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - Budget, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - Company management, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - Contract, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - Daily sales report, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - Front of house, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - Marketing, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - Press, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - WNPR, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - Samuel French, New Theatre registration, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - PBS/channel 13 Broadcasting contract, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - Press/Marketing misc., 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - Tantulus/RSC notes, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - Subscription reports, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - YSD Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - Artslink/Lilja Blumenfeld, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - Artslink/Polina Rudchik, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - PETER PAN AND WENDY
    - Contract, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
    - company management, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
    - guest artists, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
    - house management reports, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
    - performance reports, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
    - production, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
    - program and promo material, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - WHITE OAK
    - Press, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
    - Production, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
    - Program, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Box office, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Advertising, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Calendar and contact sheet, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Fleet sponsorship, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Contract, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Company management, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Location management, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Marketing, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - REVIZOR unnamed (1), 1998-1999 (Box 5)
    - Unnamed (2), 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - 1998-1999 Budgets (Box 5)
  - FEDEX, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Rep 2 GALILEO
    - Calendar and contact sheet, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
    - Sidne Anderson, Older court lady, 1998-1999
    - Licensing agreement, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
    - Guest artists, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
    - Grants, NEA, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
    - Casting, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
    - Composer, Tom Cabanis, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
    - Housing, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
    - Notes and correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Musicians, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Performance reports, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - House management reports, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Program and promo material, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Rehearsal reports, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Script, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Production notes, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - REP 3 CRUMBS FROM THE TABLE OF JOY
    - Director, Seret Scott, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - House management reports, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Calendar and contact sheet, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Guest artists, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Housing, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Casting, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Performance reports, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Production, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Program and promo material, 1998-1999 (Box 6)